{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":3900,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":29,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"If the abandon code is “Fill Main Bin Abn Excess (X),” you must verify the insert dimensions. Press F3, then type IMPRD in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IMPRD"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_81","title":"In this case, type IMPRD to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_17","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7971","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_2","Text_Entry_Box_15","SmartShape_81","Success_Shape_1","Failure_Shape_17"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7971"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_77","title":"Enter the Product number (25192207). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_49","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["25192207"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_20","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_36","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8004","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_3","SmartShape_4","SmartShape_5","SmartShape_6","SmartShape_7","SmartShape_77","Text_Entry_Box_49","Success_Shape_20","Failure_Shape_36"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8004"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_71","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_72","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_73","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_74","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":"To view the attributes of the Product (25192207), press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_76","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_48","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Slide18105","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_70","SmartShape_71","SmartShape_72","SmartShape_73","SmartShape_74","SmartShape_75","SmartShape_76","Text_Entry_Box_48"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18105"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"Next, you must compare the current case cap in IMPRD to IIPAA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8064","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_10","SmartShape_11","SmartShape_12","SmartShape_13","SmartShape_14","SmartShape_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8064"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"To compare the current case cap in IMPRD to IIPAA, press F3, then type IIPAA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_18","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIPAA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_82","title":"In this case, type IIPAA to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_18","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8124","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_16","Text_Entry_Box_18","SmartShape_82","Success_Shape_2","Failure_Shape_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8124"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"Enter the Product number (25192207). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_19","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["25192207"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_3","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_19","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8157","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_17","Text_Entry_Box_19","Success_Shape_3","Failure_Shape_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8157"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"Next, you must get an insert with the recommended dimensions. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8217","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_18","SmartShape_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8217"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"To get an insert with the recommended dimensions, press F3, then type IIAVA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_21","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIAVA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_83","title":"In this case, type IIAVA to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_4","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_20","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8277","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_20","Text_Entry_Box_21","SmartShape_83","Success_Shape_4","Failure_Shape_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8277"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"Fill in the appropriate information: Category (S), From Location (X), To Location (6), Minimum Location Height (8). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_22","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["SX68"]},"constraints":{"length":4}}}},{"id":"Text_Animation_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Animation_3","roles":{}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_21","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8310","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_22","SmartShape_21","Text_Entry_Box_22","Success_Shape_5","Failure_Shape_21"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":180},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8310"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Browse the available locations that meet the recommended insert dimensions and the yearly bin trips (X68104A3).  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8343","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_23","SmartShape_24"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8343"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":"To assign a new location (X68104A3) to the part, press F3, then type IIPAA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_24","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIPAA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_84","title":"In this case, type IIPAA to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_6","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_22","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8403","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_25","Text_Entry_Box_24","SmartShape_84","Success_Shape_6","Failure_Shape_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8403"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Enter the Product number (25192207). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_25","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["25192207"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_7","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_23","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8463","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_26","Text_Entry_Box_25","Success_Shape_7","Failure_Shape_23"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8463"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"In the “Add” screen, enter the Use code (P) and the C code (P). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_26","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["PP"]},"constraints":{"length":2}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_8","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_24","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8523","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_27","SmartShape_28","Text_Entry_Box_26","Success_Shape_8","Failure_Shape_24"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8523"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"To enter the new location, type X68104A3 in the “Location” column field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_27","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["X68104A3"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_9","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_25","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8556","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_30","SmartShape_29","Text_Entry_Box_27","Success_Shape_9","Failure_Shape_25"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8556"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"Next, you must move the material to the new bin location. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8589","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8589"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"To move the material to the new bin location, first press F3, then type ISPMH in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_29","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["ISPMH"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_85","title":"In this case, type ISPMH to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_10","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_26","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8649","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_32","Text_Entry_Box_29","SmartShape_85","Success_Shape_10","Failure_Shape_26"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8649"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"Enter the License Plate number (2415471) in the “LP” field, then press the Tab key to the “From Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_30","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["2415471"]},"constraints":{"length":7}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_11","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_27","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8682","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_33","Text_Entry_Box_30","Success_Shape_11","Failure_Shape_27"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8682"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"Press the Tab key to the “To Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_32","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Slide8715","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_34","SmartShape_35","SmartShape_36","Text_Entry_Box_32"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8715"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"Enter the Main Bin location (X68104A3) and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_33","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["X68104A3"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_12","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_28","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11661","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_37","Text_Entry_Box_33","Success_Shape_12","Failure_Shape_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11661"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"To choose the highlighted license plate and its quantity, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_34","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Slide8748","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_38","Text_Entry_Box_34"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8748"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":"Enter the quantity to move (5), then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_35","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["5"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_13","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_29","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8808","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_39","Text_Entry_Box_35","Success_Shape_13","Failure_Shape_29"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8808"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"Press Enter to assign the inventory to the new location. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_36","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Slide8868","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_40","Text_Entry_Box_36"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8868"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_61","title":"Press N for “No” in response to the “Create RF work?” message. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_45","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["N"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_62","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_63","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_19","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_35","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17564","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_61","Text_Entry_Box_45","SmartShape_62","SmartShape_63","Success_Shape_19","Failure_Shape_35"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17564"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_69","title":"Press the Esc key to exit the screen and return to the “DALLAS SYSTEM MENUS” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_47","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Slide17728","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_69","Text_Entry_Box_47"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17728"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":"To complete the abandon and the pallet move, press F3, then type RMVUC in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_37","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["RMVUC"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_86","title":"In this case, type RMVUC to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_14","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_30","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9141","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_43","Text_Entry_Box_37","SmartShape_86","Success_Shape_14","Failure_Shape_30"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9141"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":"Enter the part number (25192207), in the “Product” field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_40","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["25192207"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_15","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_31","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9174","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_44","Text_Entry_Box_40","Success_Shape_15","Failure_Shape_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9174"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_45","title":"To resolve the abandoned workunit, press the Tab key to navigate to the “Modify-dtl” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_41","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Slide9207","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_45","SmartShape_46","Text_Entry_Box_41"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9207"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":"To complete the Workunit, type C. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_52","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"AVL ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_42","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["C"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_16","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_32","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9270","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_47","SmartShape_48","SmartShape_50","SmartShape_51","SmartShape_52","Text_Caption_18","Text_Entry_Box_42","Success_Shape_16","Failure_Shape_32"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9270"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":"You have completed this process. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_60","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_79","title":"You have completed this simulation. Select the Next button below to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13341","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_59","SmartShape_60","SmartShape_79"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13341"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"FillMainBinAbnExcessTraining","class":"project","title":"FillMainBinAbnExcessTraining","children":["Slide7971","Slide8004","Slide18105","Slide8064","Slide8124","Slide8157","Slide8217","Slide8277","Slide8310","Slide8343","Slide8403","Slide8463","Slide8523","Slide8556","Slide8589","Slide8649","Slide8682","Slide8715","Slide11661","Slide8748","Slide8808","Slide8868","Slide17564","Slide17728","Slide9141","Slide9174","Slide9207","Slide9270","Slide13341"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7971","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide8004","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide18105","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide8064","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide8124","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8157","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8217","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8277","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8310","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8343","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide8403","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide8463","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide8523","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide8556","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide8589","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide8649","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide8682","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide8715","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide11661","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide8748","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide8808","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide8868","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide17564","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide17728","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide9141","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide9174","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide9207","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide9270","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide13341","title":"Slide 29"}]}